<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<message config="POCD_MT000040UV_Welcome" >
    <POCD_MT000040UV_Welcome>
        <id />
        <code />
        <title />
        <effectiveTime />
        <confidentialityCode />
        <recordTarget>
            <patientRole>
                <id />
            </patientRole>
        </recordTarget>
        <author>
            <time />
            <assignedAuthor>
                <id />
            </assignedAuthor>
        </author>
        <custodian>
            <assignedCustodian>
                <representedCustodianOrganization>
                    <id />
                </representedCustodianOrganization>
            </assignedCustodian>
        </custodian>
        <relatedDocument>
            <parentDocument>
                <id />
                <code />
            </parentDocument>
        </relatedDocument>
        <component>
            <structuredBody>
                <component>
                    <section>
                        <code />
                        <text >
                            <thumbnail>
                                <div>
									<div style="float:left;font-weight:bold;font-size:15pt;">
										To: <span id="patientId" style="color: #5D2A8F;text-decoration: underline;"></span>
									</div>
									<div style="font-weight:bold;font-size:15pt;margin-left:350px;">
										Subject: Welcome to Eternity
										<br/><br/>
									</div>
									<div style="font-size:12pt;">
										Dear <span id="patientName"></span>
									</div><br/><br/>
									<div style="font-size:12pt;">
										Please allow us to personally welcome you to the Eternity Membership Program. We at Eternity believe that Life is precious and by taking the
										Eternity proactive approach you can safe guard your life and those who you love.  
										<br/><br/>
										We are proud to be one of the most advanced screening and testing centers in the world. By measuring and monitoring hundreds of 
										biomarkers, health indicators and hormones, you can rest assured that you are giving your body the care it deserves for a healthier and happier
										life.
										<br/><br/>
										At Eternity we employ three simple, yet effective step to ensure your body receives the respect it deserves.
										<br/><br/>
										Step one: MEASURE We measure, depending on your Program your Biomarkers, Health Indicators and Hormones at regular intervals. This
										can help detect early life  threatening situations such as Cardio-Metabolic Disease, Cancer, Diabetes, Alzheimer's and other. By keeping you in
										'The Eternity Zone' (E- Zone) which is an area of optimal health, we help protect you against chronic disease.
										<br/><br/>
										Step two: MENTOR At Eternity we believe that each person is an individual, and this is why our eight part Integral Health Program is tailored
										to each client. With evidence-based knowledge and wisdom we focus on ensuring health for your wellbeing.
										<br/><br/>
										Step three: MONITOR We monitor through Eternity's propriety LHAMP (Lifestyle Health Assessment and Monitoring Program). We evaluate 
										your subjective feelings and objective biomarkers to ensure you stay within the E- Zone of wellbeing. We are honored that you have chosen
										Eternity to be "Your Personal Age Manager".
										<br/><br/>
										Please click <a href="http://119.226.87.12/hin-web/"><u>here</u></a> to login.
										<br/><br/>
										Yours in Health,
										<br/><br/><br/>
									</div>
								</div>
							</thumbnail>
                        </text>
                    </section>
                </component>
            </structuredBody>
        </component>
    </POCD_MT000040UV_Welcome>
</message>